Inspector: Ah, come in.
Barbara: Thank you.
Inspector: Can you confirm your name, please?
Barbara: Yes, I’m Barbara Travers.
Inspector: OK, Miss Travers, what did you do after dinner yesterday evening?
Barbara: After dinner?
I played cards with Gordon, and then I went to bed.
Inspector: What time was that?
Barbara: It was about half past eleven.
I remember, I looked at my watch.
Inspector: Did you hear anything in your father’s room?
Barbara: No. I didn’t hear anything.
Inspector: Miss Travers, did you have any problems with your father?
Barbara: No, I didn’t have any problems with him at all.
Daddy was a wonderful man,
a wonderful father.
Sorry, Inspector.
Inspector: OK, Miss Travers.
No more questions.
Could you ask Mr. Summers to come in, please?
Barbara: Of course.
Inspector: Mr. Summers.
Gordon: Call me Gordon.
Inspector: Thank you, uh … Gordon.
What did you do after dinner?
Gordon: I played cards with Barbara.
And then she went to bed.
Inspector: Did you go to bed then?
Gordon: No. I stayed in the living room and then I went to bed.
Inspector: What time was that?
Gordon: I don’t remember exactly.
I didn’t look at the time.
Inspector: Did you hear anything during the night?
Gordon: No, I didn’t.
I was very tired.
I slept very well.
Inspector: You and Mr. Travers were business partners, weren’t you?
Gordon: Yes, that’s right.
Inspector: And it’s a very good business, I understand.
Gordon: Yes, Inspector, it is.
Inspector: And now it’s your business.
Gordon: Listen, Inspector, I did not kill Jeremy.
He was my partner and he was my friend.
Inspector: Very well, Gordon.
Could you ask Ms. Pasquale to come in, please?
Gordon: Certainly.
Inspector: Ah, good morning Miss...
Claudia: Pasquale.
Claudia Pasquale.
Inspector: Take a seat, Ms. Pasquale.
Claudia: Thank you.
Inspector: So, Ms. Pasquale, what did you do after dinner yesterday evening?
Claudia: I went to my room and I had a bath and I went to bed.
Inspector: What time was that?
Claudia: About 11 o’clock.
Inspector: Did you hear anything?
Claudia: Yes. I heard somebody go into Jeremy’s room.
It was about twelve o’clock.
Inspector: Who was it?
Claudia: It was Amanda, his wife.
Inspector: Are you sure? Did you see her?
Claudia: Well, no, I didn’t see her.
But I’m sure it was Amanda.
Inspector: You were Mr. Travers’s secretary, weren't you, Claudia?
Claudia: Yes, I was.
Inspector: Were you just his secretary?
Claudia: What do you mean?
Inspector: Were you in love with Mr. Travers, Claudia?
Claudia: No, I wasn’t.
Inspector: The truth please, Claudia.
Claudia: Very well, Inspector.
Yes, I was in love with him, and he said that he was in love with me.
He said he wanted to leave his wife – Amanda – and marry me.
I was stupid. I believed him.
But he didn’t leave her.
He used me, Inspector!
I was very angry with him.
Inspector: Did you kill him?
Claudia: No, Inspector.
I loved Jeremy.